But just for... is it rolling?
Nah, so...
Where are we?
Point to a beauty parlor.
We have all these beauty parlor for men.
Alright, so...
You see the beauty parlor?
They're very gay.
Who use... I don't need... I don't need no fucking beauty parlor.
Or I need water and salt.
What?
This is really...
You know, if you think part of this is it, it is pretty...
No?
I'm talking with you, but I'm not with the camera.
Yes, indeed.
So, for me...
Where is all you was not?
For all I was...
To...
Right, right, right.
This is absolutely fucking fair.
Absolutely.
Do not drink anything colorful.
What about this one?
That's different.
It's normal.
Yeah.
So, comfortable.
No smell, smell, it's...
This is definitely just a little bit gay.
You know why?
Because I love oranges, but real, like natural oranges.
You know?
And fabricated oranges is absolutely very gay.
You make it yourself, you know?
Yes.
Orndroes, but natural, or bringing oranges, like your grandma can just squeeze the...
Like to make lemonade, yeah.
Like, so many other things.
But this is gay.
I like what they do.
Not for all me.
Oh, sorry.
So, anything, if you want to drink fucking alcohol,
do not go for alcohol-free drinks.
Like, what's the point?
Why do you drink beer if there's no alcohol inside?
Like, just please.
I don't know.
Do you drink beer without a...
I drink beer straight out the cake.
There you go, you're not gay.
Fucking hell, look at this.
Anyway, I'll know if there's alcohol-free, but...
Alcohol-free.
You just really say something.
That's so hard.
So, snacks.
When we talk about snacks, you need to only eat fruits.
Right?
None of these are applicable in your case.
Just, you don't be strong, like, less hard drive food.
Drive food?
I guess it's tolerable.
No?
No, it's okay.
But, fucking, look.
It's nice.
Every cancer is.
Don't.
Now, we don't discriminate food, right?
We love food, but...
We're not eating the cancer food.